marriage is tough it is marriage is hard
but it's worth it it's totally worth it
you know besides i don't want to be out
there single again trying to date at my
age
i don't i saw an article that said if
you want to meet someone a good place to
go is the grocery store
what am i gonna put on some smooth moves
at the whole foods now
can't try to hit on a woman at the
grocery store you gotta worry about what
you're gonna say you gotta worry about
what you're gonna wear and now you gotta
worry about what's in your basket
i can't be trying to hit on a woman she
looks down my basket see some lactose
free milk breathe right strips and roach
spray
i'm not a recipe for romance
and you can't try too hard with the
items in your basket you can have like
some champagne and some strawberries and
some whipped cream
you're like yeah girl i got some
strawberries and whipped cream i just
need one more thing
she's like yeah you need a pound cake is
what you need
why don't you roll on down to the bakery
section
hold on how about we pop open a little
bit of the bubbly uh i'm gonna skip the
toasted and go straight to the ghosting
okay
some women like a big burly man to
protect them and keep them safe and then
there's women like my wife who's
apparently content to take her chances
she knows that their trouble to shove me
to the attacker and run
i'm not trying to look like this i want
to be bigger i joined a boot camp class
at the encouragement of groupon
they had me out there running around the
field trying to flip a truck tire
i'm like um i'm gonna need something
from a smaller truck
and i get this boy a tonka
i can't flip a truck time i can't flip a
mattress
we have a king-sized mattress you ever
tried to flip a king-sized mattress by
yourself
it's like setting a human-sized rat trap
i got it i got it i got it oh i don't
get it
[Applause]
i want to be big
i want to take steroids i do
i think steroids should be legal if
you're over 40 and married
i mean i already have all the side
effects
might as well be jacked
go around open up pickle jars
let me get my swole on
but i'm thin so i try to make the most
of it uh my wife and i went to a costume
party i had a great costume i wore some
black spandex one red glove one white
glove and went as a jumper cable
is
[Music]
you